Evil lives within you
The Taking of Deborah Logan is a horror, mystery film directed by Adam Robitel.
What starts as a poignant medical documentary about Deborah Logan's descent into Alzheimer's disease and her daughter's struggles as caregiver degenerates into a maddening portrayal of
dementia at its most frightening, as hair-raising events begin to plague the family and crew and an unspeakable malevolence threatens to tear the very fabric of sanity from them all.
Deborah Logan, played by Jill Larson.
Sarah Logan, played by Anne Ramsay.
Mia Hu, played by Michelle Ang.
Harris, played by Ryan Cutrona.
Dr. Nazir, played by Anne Bedian.
Gavin, played by Brett Gentile.
The Taking of Deborah Logan is a 2014 American found footage supernatural horror film, which serves as the feature film
directorial debut of Adam Robitel, who co-wrote the screenplay and edited the film with Gavin Heffernan.
The film stars Jill Larson, Anne Ramsay and Michelle Ang.
Set in Virginia, it tells the story of a documentary crew making a film about Alzheimer's
patients who uncover something sinister while documenting a woman who has the disease.
The film was produced by Jeff Rice and Bryan Singer
and was released on October 21, 2014.
The film explores themes of snake, halloween,
possession, serial killer, found footage.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.